ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
本周四沃特电视 女性频道
This Thursday on VTV: Television for Women...
我认为我是在找寻一种
I guess I'm just searching for
更有意义的生活 阿达纳先生
a more purposeful life, Mr. Adana.
ShinY
深影
集众教会
The Church of the Collective
能给你提供很多很多
can offer you so much more.
■
ShinY
深影
■
翻译：  黑猫 鸭梨安安 siren 锅仔 大瓜咕
我们可以给你一个家
We can offer you a family.
■
校对：  负零     压制： 青鸟
阿达纳先生 请实话告诉我
Mr. Adana, tell me the truth.
你在跟踪我吗
Are you having me followed?
我得知道
I had to find out
ShinY
深影
■
你是否将教会摆在第一位
if you were putting the Church first,
摆在你的事业之前
before your career.
摆在所有事之前
Before everything.
你将你的首字母烙印在我身上
You branded me with your initials!
够了
It's enough.
恐怕你已经
I am afraid that you have become
ShinY
深影
变得恶毒 深海
a toxic personality, Deep.
ShinY
深影
我别无选择只能逃跑
Then you've left me no choice but to run.
必须带上海豚
Not Without My Dolphin.
苗条淑女冷冻晚餐赞助 沃特出品
Brought to you by Lean Lady frozen dinners, by Vought.
今晚 沃特旗下各大电视台
Tonight, simulcast live across VBS, VTV, VNN,
将会同步直播
Vought Soul and Voughtemundo,
我的年度《生日盛宴》节目 敬请收看
join me for my annual Birthday Spectacular,
联合队长星光也将到场
along with my cocaptain Starlight,
以及艾梅里尔·拉加西
as well as Emeril Lagasse,
流氓弗拉德乐队 超音速
Rascal Flatts, Supersonic,
《河谷镇》演员 朱迪·丹奇女爵
the cast of Riverdale, Dame Judi Dench
当然了 还有我亲爱的朋友玄色
and, of course, my dear friend Black Noir...
嗨 威廉
Hey, William.
该死的药贩子 我说的对吗
Goddamn the pusher man, am I right?
你真的要把那个玩意打入体内
You really gonna shoot that shit in your veins?
我觉得我可能会
You know, I think I just might.
你很可能尖叫着死去
Odds are you'll die screaming.
我冒过更大的风险
Well, I've gambled more for less.
我觉得你不会这么做
I don't think you're gonna do it.
把自己变成一个超人类
Turn yourself into a Supe?
即使对你来说都有点没底线了
That's a new low, even for you.
还可以再低一点儿
Oh, I can go lower.
下地狱都行
I can go straight to hell.
布彻 你不能再这么下去了
Butcher, you have to stop.
拜托 就算是为了贝卡 会伤透她的心的
Please. For Becca. This would break her heart.
贝卡才不在乎
Becca don't care what I do.
她已经死了
She's dead.
你好 亲爱的 是不是有点早了
Hello, love. A bit early, isn't it?
你说过八点后可以打电话 现在是八点零三分
You said I could call you after 8:00. It's 8:03.
哦 你说得对
Ah, yeah. Right you are.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
很好 一切平安 为什么
Yeah. Hunky-dory. Why?
你看起来很疲惫
You look tired.
只是 昨晚过得很糟
Ah, just, uh, had a naff night, that's all.
没有睡觉
No sleep.
你看我做的视频了吗
Did you watch the video I made?
还没有
Uh, no, no.
我还没机会看
I, uh... I ain't had a chance yet.
我觉得你应该看看
I think you should watch it.
我睡不好的时候那些视频能帮到我
It kind of helps me when I don't sleep so good.
好的 听着 我说了会晚点再看的
Yeah, look, I told you I'll watch it later.
你生我的气了吗
Are you mad at me?
没有
No, uh...
当然没有了
of course not.
听着 你是你妈妈的儿子
Look, you're your mother's son.
我会永远照顾你的
And I'll always watch out for you.
就像我承诺过的那样
Just how I promised.
好吗
All right?
你好啊 瞌睡虫
Hey there, sleepyhead.
该起床啦 今天是个大日子
Rise and shine. Big day.
今天有什么特别的吗
Anything a little extra special about today? Hmm?
今天是我的生日 傻瓜
It's my birthday, silly.
如果你想祝我生日快乐就眨眨眼
Okay, just blink if you want to wish me a happy birthday, hmm?
好吧
Okay.
所以红河是沃特子公司持有的
Okay, so Red River is a group home
一家福利院
owned by a Vought subsidiary, of course.
我猜维琪就是在那里长大的
I guess that's where Vicky grew up.
你的意思是纳蒂亚
You mean Nadia?
天呐 我真是个傻瓜 我早该料到的
God, I'm a fucking idiot. I should have seen it.
- 你怎么能料到这些 - 我不知道
- How could you have seen this? - I don't know.
或许当她杀了瑞尼或者炸毁国会的时候
Maybe when she killed Rayner or when she blew up Congress.
该死
Goddamn it.
也许我们应该透露给《纽约时报》
Maybe we leak it to The Times.
不行 她会爆了办公室里每个人的头 包括我
No, she could head-pop everybody in the office, me included.
等等 等等 你要去吗
Wait, wait, you're going in?
- 就说你病了 - 我们
- Call in sick. - We...
我们三点有一场全体会议
We have an all-hands at 3:00.
我每次都参加
I've never missed one before.
如果我们告诉布彻呢
What if we tell Butcher?
告诉布彻我给一个超人类当了一年的副手
We tell Butcher I've been a Supe's sidekick for a year?
他肯定会折磨我一辈子的 是吧
Oh, Christ, he's never gonna not torture me for this, is he?
也许不会
Well, maybe he won't.
不 不 不 听着 我们可以自己解决
No. No, no, no. Look, we can... handle this ourselves.
好吗
All right?
什么都别做
Just don't do anything.
- 疯狂 愚蠢的事吗 - 不
- What, crazy, stupid? - No.
我回来前什么事也不要做
Don't do anything until I get back.
- 好吗 - 你要走吗
- Okay? - You're leaving?
对 去为祖国人愚蠢的
Yeah, it's the soundcheck
生日特别节目彩排
for Homelander's stupid birthday special.
等我
Wait for me.
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
当然了
Sure.
这边一下 那边一下
And pop, pop.
摆头
Head slide.
今晚我会滑步 谢谢
I'll slide tonight. Thank you.
宝刀未老
Whew! Still got it.
你又找回了《我想那么甜》巡演时的状态
Looks like you're back on the "Sweet As I Wanna Be" Tour.
不 这太丢人了
Oh, wow. No, this is humiliating.
我十八岁唱这首歌时就觉得恶心
That song was gross when I was 18.
我如今再唱 他们会
I sing it now, they're gonna
让我远离学校的
make me keep a thousand feet from schools.
那就别唱
Then don't sing it.
拒绝对你来说很容易
That's easy for you to say.
你已经加入七人队了
You're already in The Seven.
我不想引起轩然大波
I... I don't want to make waves.
信我 去掀起风浪吧
Trust me... make waves.
杰 我现在可以彩排吗
Hey, Jay, um, could we run my segment now, actually?
因为我只有几句台词而已
'Cause I only have a few lines.
当然了 可以
Of course. Yeah.
你的激情呢 星光
Where's the fire, Starlight?
怎么 你在休息吗
What, are you on a break?
- 先生 生日快乐 我是 - 超音速
- Sir, happy birthday. I'm... - Supersonic, right?
是的
Yeah, that's right.
- 很高兴遇见你 - 我也是
- Great to meet you. - You, too.
在《美国英雄》里 你是强有力的竞争者
You're a real, uh, contender on American Hero.
保持住 我们可能成为队友
Keep it up. We could be teammates.
希望如此 先生
Oh, wow, I hope so, sir.
当然 节目的评委曾经
Of course, it doesn't hurt that the show's judge
陷入你的温柔乡不会有什么影响
used to get come-drunk on your chorizo picante.
祖国人 先生 我们在加载
Homelander, sir, we're loading
- 星光修订后的提示词 - 好的
- the prompter with Starlight's revisions. - Sure.
- 修订 - 是的
- Revisions? - Yeah.
我让布鲁斯做了一些调整
I had Bruce make a couple of tweaks,
- 加了些更有趣的东西 - 不
- gave you some more juicy stuff. - No.
毕竟你是联合队长
After all, you are cocaptain.
得让你更重要一些
Need you front and center.
- 罗杰 放到提词器上 - 好的 先生
- Roger, cue these up. - Yes, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道
You know,
我得承认
I got to admit,
之前我有些不确定
I was a little unsure about this.
但现在
But now,
说实话 对于即将发生的事我太兴奋了
honestly, I am just so excited about what's coming.
搭档
Partner.
准备排练
Ready for rehearsal.
还好吗 伙计
All right, mate?
天呐 珍妮 你长得真快
Bloody hell, Janine. You shot up.
你还记得你比利叔叔吧
You remember your Uncle Billy, don't you?
给你
Here.
我给你买了这个
I got this for you.
你可以爸爸一起拼
You and your dad can build it together.
五百二十三块 家庭娱乐
523 pieces of family fun.
第一 你不能突然来访
Okay, one, you don't just pop up here.
得先打电话
You call first.
第二 士兵男孩去死吧
And, two, eff Soldier Boy.
我一点也不在乎他是怎么死的
I don't give a mothereffin' doo-doo how he checked out.
胡说
Ah, bollocks.
他死的不像是个英雄
He didn't die like no hero.
我打赌他是跪着去死的
I'll wager he went out on his knees,
像个婊子一样祈求着
begging like a right cunt.
什么鬼
What the f...
抱歉 亲爱的
Sorry, love.
听着
Look,
如果有武器可以杀死士兵男孩
if there's a weapon out there that killed Soldier Boy,
那也可以杀死祖国人
then it can kill Homelander.
值得我们查一查
And that's got to be worth something.
现在
Now,
我们正在调查他之前的队伍
we're working our way through his old team.
弗兰基和山崎纪从绯红伯爵夫人开始
Frenchie and Kimiko are starting with the Crimson Countess,
我去查查火药
and I'm gonna hit up Gunpowder.
听起来你已胸有成竹
Sounds like you got everything covered.
让你调查的不是别人
This ain't just anyone.
是士兵男孩
It's Soldier Boy.
你可以彻彻底底的和他做个了断
You could close the book on him once and for all.
为了你的父亲 你的家人
For your dad. Your family.
去他妈的
Fuck off with that shit.
我父亲蜷缩在桌子上死去
My father died hunched over a desk,
痴迷于一个已死之人
obsessing over a dead man,
却忽视了他的两个活生生的孩子
while he was ignoring his two living children.
我差点也对我女儿做出同样的事情
And I almost did the same thing to her.
谢谢你的到来
Thanks for coming by.
你是个好父亲 伙计
You're doing a bang-up job with her, mate.
布彻 等一下
Butcher, hold on a second.
我可能有个线索
I might have one thing.
欢迎来到无畏梅芙的包容王国
Welcome to Brave Maeve's Inclusive Kingdom.
别忘了取你和无畏梅芙的照片
Don't forget to get your photo with Brave Maeve.
- 你是真正的英雄 - 笑一个
- You're the real hero. - Smile.
这里有棉花糖
Cotton candy here.
甜甜圈汉堡 新鲜出炉的
Doughnut burgers. Get your hot doughnut burgers.
甜甜圈做成的汉堡包
Que c'est... Hamburger with a doughnut for a bun?
简直太离谱了
Truly, there is no God here.
祖国人: 极限飞行
Homelander: Extreme Flight.
我们能去吗
Can we go??
拜托 为了三分钟的过山车
Come on. You want to wait three hours
等三个小时吗 而且还是纪念这个禽兽的
for a three-minute ride that is a monument to a monster?
- 我一直想坐 - 什么时候啊
- I always wanted to! - Since when?
我和健二小时候
Since Kenji and I were little.
好吧 先工作再玩
Okay, first, work, then pleasure.
来吧
Let's go. Come on.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
亲爱的
Mon coeur.
士兵男孩: 音乐之旅
"Soldier Boy: A Musical Journey"
即将开启
is about to begin.
现在就来买票吧
Get your tickets now.
士兵男孩在
Soldier Boy grew up
美国自由的发源地长大
in the birthplace of American liberty.
出生在南费城破旧的主街道上
Born poor on the mean streets of South Philadelphia,
他实践了勤奋 坚韧 勇敢的价值观
he learned the values of hard work, tenacity and bravery.
他用这些价值观 向世界证明了
He used those values to prove America's exceptionalism
美国的优越性
to the world.
兄弟们 给我揍这些德国鬼子
Okay, boys, let's give these Krauts some hell.
他保护我们
He defended us
免受红色威胁的入侵
against the encroaching Red Menace.
议员
Congress,
我这里有一张公开的共产主义者名单
I have a list right here of avowed Communists.
他帮助引导美国
He helped guide America
走向更光明的未来 在这条路上
into a brighter future, and along the way,
他找到了一份来自优秀女人的爱
he found the love of a good woman,
这份爱让他的牺牲变得更加崇高
which made his sacrifice all the more noble,
他献出了自己的生命 拯救民众于核灾难
when he gave his life saving us from a nuclear holocaust.
请一起向士兵男孩致敬
Please join us in saluting Soldier Boy.
下一个
Next!
你们已经过了看绯红伯爵夫人节目的年纪吧
You seem a little old for the Countess Tea Package.
我们的内心还很年轻
We're young at heart.
我喜欢你的音乐
哦 亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
你不能说话吗
Can't you talk?
想听点新的吗
Would you like to hear something new?
你知道黑猩猩生来是不会哭的吗
You know that chimps are physically incapable of crying?
但这不代表它们内心没有哭泣
But that doesn't mean they're not crying on the inside.
她人很好
She's nice.
她是个疯子
She's nuts!
不 她不是
No, she's not.
快点把活干完
Let's get it over with!
好吧
Fine.
你在干
Wh-What are you...
你在干什么
Wh-What are you... Ow!
不要让她双手接触
Don't let her hands touch!
放开我 你个贱人
Ow! Let go of me, you bitch.
手碰不到就没有火球 是吧
No fireball if your hands don't touch, oui?
你安静地待着 放松点
You stay quiet and relax.
- 她会伤害你 - 你们想要什么
- She will hurt you. - What do you want?
我们想了解士兵男孩
We want to know about Soldier Boy.
你们他妈的怎么关心起士兵男孩了
What the fuck do you care about Soldier Boy?
我们想知道真相
We want the truth about Soldier Boy,
而不是你那糟糕的节目中的狗屎
not the merde you've been giving us in your appalling show.
他怎么死的 谁杀了他 说话
How did he die? Who killed him? Talk.
节目说的就是真相 混蛋
The show is the truth, motherfucker.
可以和伯爵夫人待三分钟
Three minutes with the Countess.
他牺牲得很英勇
He died a hero.
- 玩得开心 - 谢谢
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
来吧
Allez.
我们得走了 快
We got to go. Come on.
该死的
Goddamn it.
日
Fuck!
天
God...
休伊 伙计
Hughie, my man.
有事吗
You okay?
阿莱克斯
A-Alex? Uh...
安妮呢
Uh, where's Annie?
她和祖国人在舞台上
She's actually onstage with Homelander.
今天真他妈疯狂 伙计
It's a crazy fucking day, man.
对啊 我很高兴你能陪着她
Yeah, yeah. Uh, so glad that you're-you're there with her.
嘿 你为什么 你为什么接电话
Um, hey, why'd you, uh... why'd you pick up the phone?
你三分钟打了三次电话
Well, you called three times in the last three minutes.
- 出什么事了吗 - 没有 一切都好
- Is anything wrong? - No, no, everything's good.
没事 告诉她我打过电话 好吗
Everything's fine. Just tell her that I called, okay?
今晚 很荣幸与各位共聚一堂
It is such an honor to be with you all tonight,
为我亲爱的朋友和导师祖国人庆生
celebrating my... my dear friend and mentor Homelander.
在请出朱迪·丹奇女爵之前
Now, before we bring out Dame Judi Dench,
我想花点时间
I would like to take a moment...
杰 那是什么
Uh, hey, Jay. What's that?
我应该宣布星光之家的成立
I'm supposed to be announcing the Starlight House.
你为我唱生日歌
You sing me "Happy Birthday."
好玩吧
Fun, right?
来吧 唱吧
Go on. Go for it.
等下 抱歉
Hold on, hold on, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
星光
Um, Starlight.
听着 星光 我
Listen, Starlight, I-I...
我讨厌这样指挥你 但我们需要
...hate to direct you, but, um, we're gonna need a little more
梦露为肯尼迪唱生日歌的那种感觉
"JFK just got rimmed out by Marilyn" Version.
要和表演相配
It's got to fit with the routine.
给她看一下表演吧
A-Actually, show her the routine.
你肯定喜欢
You're gonna fucking love this.
- 这是你的伴舞 - 好吧
- That's your backup. - Okay...
各位 稍等
Okay, uh, hold on, everybody.
女士们 谢谢 退下吧 好吗
Okay, ladies, thank you. Just stand down, okay?
很快回来
Real quick.
我可以和罗杰谈谈吗
Can I talk to Roger?
- 行 当然 - 有什么问题吗
- Uh, yeah, sure, abso... - Problem?
我很
I have...
担心
concerns.
是吗
- You do? - Mm-hmm.
好吧 担心什么呢
Oh, okay, well, uh, what are they?
- 有失尊严 - 给朋友唱一首生日歌
- It's demeaning. - It's demeaning
有失尊严吗
to sing your friend "Happy Birthday"?
你会在我的生日时性感地唱歌吗
Are you gonna sing all sexy for me on my birthday?
星光 你为什么这么抵触呢
Starlight, where... wh-what's with all this animosity?
可以让我们单独谈一下吗
Hey, um, can we just have one minute, please?
- 可以 走吧 - 谢谢
- Yes. Go. - Thank you.
听好了
- For the record... - Mm-hmm.
我知道你不在乎我唱不唱歌
I know you don't care whether I sing or not.
这种幼稚的做法
This is a juvenile attempt
让我看起来像个性玩偶 而不是联合队长
to get me to look like a sex doll instead of a cocaptain.
我不会照做
I'm not doing it.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
你他妈的怎么不放轻松点
Why don't you lighten the fuck up?
来吧 你们要唱这首歌
Come on, you're gonna sing the shit out of this song.
- 准备好了吗 唱吧 - 如果星光
- Ready? Let's hit it. - If Starlight
不想唱 不许逼她唱
doesn't want to sing, she doesn't sing.
斯坦 真是惊喜
Stan. What a surprise.
测试表明 百分之七十六的潜在观众
Our testing shows that 76% of likely viewers
今晚都会尽量抽空来看星光
will make every effort to watch tonight for Starlight.
至于你 百分之五十三的人也许会看录播
As for you, 53% might DVR.
我想这意味着她可以
I think that that means that she can
自己决定 不是吗
call her own shots. Don't you?
那我走 斯坦 百分率会怎么样
So how about I just walk, Stan? How would that rate?
在你去年陷入自己挖的公关坑后
After the PR hole you dug for yourself this past year,
我想说 你很幸运我们能上演这场生日闹剧
I'd say you're lucky we're putting on this farce at all.
不过 这是你的派对 你想哭也可以
But hey, it's your party. You can cry if you want to.
天 安妮
- Damn, Annie. - Hmm.
你在纽约做了什么
What happened to you in New York?
我开始制造风波
I started making waves.
感谢你们前来
Thank you so much for coming in.
你们见过我的新开发主管了吗
Have you met my new development exec?
嗨 我也叫艾什丽
Hi. I'm also Ashley.
我们很好奇 你们今天准备了什么
We are super curious to hear what you have for us today.
- 非常好奇 - 我想了很多
- Mm-hmm. So curious. - I've been thinking a lot
关于我怎么样才能做出贡献
about all the ways that I can contribute around here.
也许我不能像以前跑得那么快了
Maybe I can't run as fast as I used to,
但我从来不只是跑得最快的人
but I've never just been the world's fastest man.
火车头有很多
Like, there's a lot of layers to the A-Train
不为人知的特性
that people haven't seen yet.
比如呢
Such as?
我也是一个坚强 自豪的黑人
Well, I'm also a-a strong, very proud Black man.
是吧 赛斯
Right, Seth?
赛斯 拜托 伙计
Seth, come on, man.
告诉他们
Tell them.
好吧
Right. Um...
七人队对于非裔美国人的宣传做得并不好
The Seven have been dipping in the African American demo.
七人队的黎明的票房不是很好
Our numbers for Dawn of The Seven have been soft.
有色人种并不喜欢纳粹
People of color don't tend to react well to Nazis.
- 是事实 - 我们认为重塑火车头的形象
- Facts. - We thought a rebranding of A-Train
可能会改变现状
maybe could change that.
如果做得有品位的话
If done tastefully.
- 意味着重塑 - 所以
- A rebranding. - So, listen,
我们先在沃特灵魂频道播放纪录片
we start with a docuseries on Vought Soul.
火车头去非洲
A-Train to Africa.
这幅画
- Boom. - The art's, uh,
只是个模拟
just a mock-up.
纪录片将跟随着他家人的旅途
It'll trace his family's journey
从非洲平原一直到沃特大厦
from the plains of Africa all the way to Vought Tower.
我想来一场寻根之旅
Yeah, like, I want to get back in touch with my roots.
就像《根》
Like in Roots.
对Z世代来说
And for the Gen Z's,
是一次极富艺术性的交互学习体验
a state-of-the-art interactive learning experience.
这是关于奴隶贸易的游戏吗
Is that a video game about the slave trade?
非常厉害
It's some powerful stuff.
非常棒
It's really something.
我甚至让LJ重新设计了衣服
I even had LJ redesign the suit.
为了黑人文化
You know, for the culture.
- 我想在今晚就展示它 - 大可不必
- I want to introduce it tonight. - Oh, yeah, no,
我们再考虑考虑
Let's have a beat on that and think about that.
- 好  - 好的
- Okay. Wow. - Okay.
非常感谢你的这份激情
Thank you so much for that pitch.
讲得太好了
That was so well told.
说得好极了
Mm-hmm. So well told.
好吧 没错
All right. Yeah.
我们会与团队讨论一番
We're gonna discuss with the team
然后再回复你
and-and get back to you.
酷 好的 谢谢
Cool. Yeah. Thanks.
今晚见
See you tonight.
我有点惊讶她们刚才没吃这一套
I'm kind of surprised that they didn't buy it in the room.
她讨厌这个
She hated it.
什么 不可能
What? No.
伙计 她说那个想法"说得好"
Man, she said it was "Well told."
对 那他妈是代表她讨厌的意思
Yeah, that's code for she fucking hated it.
伙计 她没吃这套是因为这完全是胡说八道
Look, man, she didn't buy it because it's total bullshit.
你才不在乎你的非洲血统
You couldn't care less about your African roots.
你知道 她也知道 坦率地说 非洲也知道
You know it, and she knows it, and frankly, Africa knows it.
是吗
Yeah?
你个没屌的怂货
You don't have a fucking dick.
你在沃特做什么工作呢
So, uh, where at Vought do you work?
在大楼里做社交媒体 四十七层
Um, uh, the Tower, social media, up on 47th.
不好意思 你说想收养孩子的父母没多少
Um, I'm sorry, you said you don't get
是什么意思
many potential parents?
你知道我们是什么福利院 对吧
Well, you know what kind of a home we are, right?
是的 不 当然 超人类儿童
Yeah, no, of course, it's a group home...
福利院
...for the s-super-abled.
梅森 请从那里下来
Mason, please get down from there.
是啊 有很多悲惨的故事
Yeah, uh, so many tragic stories,
但是加以正确教导
but, uh, with the right attention,
他们很快就能回归正轨
uh, they can bounce back so quickly.
是的 他们是小宝藏
Yeah, they're little treasures.
天哪
Geez.
泰迪·斯蒂威尔 不许瞬移
Teddy Stillwell, we don't teleport.
- 我可以玩我的玩具吗 - 可以
- Can I play with my toys? - Yeah.
所以 他们...他们的父母 他们是...
So, their-their parents, they're, uh...
有一些孩子
Well, uh, some of the kids,
在可以控制能力之前
they discovered their gifts quite early,
就已经发现了自己的天赋
before they were able to control them.
但听着 我保证你会非常安全
But listen, I-I'm sure you'd be perfectly safe.
红毯上星光璀璨
嘿 你能...
Hey, can you...
你... 能带我看看其它地方吗
Can you, uh... can you show me the rest of the place?
- 你想看什么 - 什么都好
- Uh, what did you want to see? - Anything.
有什么都可以给我看
Whatever you got.
抱歉 怎么了 泰迪
Sorry, what, uh... what is it, Teddy?
等一下 我认识你
Hey, wait a minute. I know you.
你是星光的男朋友
You're Starlight's boyfriend?
你在局里工作
And you work at the bureau.
- 不 我可以... - 这太不合规范了
- Uh... No, no, I can... - This is highly irregular.
我可以解释
Hey, hey, I-I can explain.
好吧 事实是...
Um, okay, the-the truth is...
是星光让我来的
Starlight is-is the one that sent me here.
我不育 医生说我的精子质量很差
I'm completely sterile. Doctor says my sperm are bad.
真的很差劲
Like, really, really bad,
就像一群肥大的死蝌蚪
like a bunch of fat, dead tadpoles.
但是我们想要孩子 而且她想保密
But we-we want a kid, and, um, she wanted to keep it quiet,
所以她派我来给她打掩护
so she sent me here to cover for her.
顺便说一句 我从没来过这里
I-I was never here, by the way.
我们只是想保证是出于爱 而非宣传
We just want to keep it about love and not publicity.
你懂的吧
You know?
太棒了 有个超人类妈妈
This is fantastic. With a superhuman mother,
父母死亡的可能性要小得多
there is far less chance of parental fatality.
这太棒了...
Oh, yeah. That's great...
是个好消息
That's great news.
我有一些杰出的孩子
So, I have a few standouts
你们肯定喜欢
that I think you'll be pretty thrilled with.
你介意我... 自己翻翻看吗
You mind if I, uh, just kind of flip around a bit?
谢谢 抱歉 借光
Thank you. Thank you. Sorry. Move this over.
抱歉
Sorry.
有什么特殊要求吗
Is there anything in particular that you're looking for?
男孩还是女孩
Um, boy, girl?
没有 我们倒没有多在乎性别
No, you know, we don't really see gender that way.
萨米尔来自南亚
Well, Samir is South Asian.
现在那里特别热
That is very hot right now.
不 听起来很棒 萨米尔
No, that sounds great. Wh... Uh, Samir...
- 是她吗 - 南亚人
- Right here? Okay. - South Asian.
纳蒂亚 你知道今天为什么来这里吗
Nadia, do you know why you're here today?
我做错什么了吗
Did I do something wrong?
没有 你进步很大
Not at all. You've made so much progress.
所以你才来这里
That's why you're here.
你就要得偿所愿了
You're getting what you've always wanted.
你要领养我吗
You're-you're adopting me?
不 严格来说我不能领养你 动力
No, I can't adopt you, sport, not technically.
非常复杂 你就别担心了
It's more complicated than you need to worry about.
不过 你是个非常罕见且出众的女孩
But you are a very rare and exceptional girl,
你跟我走吧
and you're coming with me.
我会照顾你的
I'm gonna take care of you now.
可以吗
Is that all right?
"这是可怕的 恐怖的
"It has been a terrible, horrible,
不好的 糟糕的一天
no good, very bad day.
我妈妈说有些日子就是这样
My mom says some days are like that.
即使是在澳大利亚"
Even in Australia."
你要我再读一遍吗
You want me to read it again?
- 我已经太老了 - 聪明的小坏蛋
- Actually too old for that. - Oh, you smart-ass.
去吧  让我和你妈妈聊聊
Scoot. Let me talk to your mom.
糟糕的日子确实有
Bad days do happen.
也许我需要给你读读这个
Maybe I need to read this to you.
你读过了 睡前都读过一百万遍了
You have. About a million times before bed.
- 有什么新闻吗 - 依然没有
- Anything in the news? - Still nothing.
好
Good.
托尼是你的朋友
Tony was a friend of yours.
我明白你为什么生气
I understand why you'd be upset.
沃特的人彻底搞砸了
Somebody at Vought dropped the ball.
我不能让人出现在我办公室 叫我纳蒂亚
I can't have people showing up at my work calling me Nadia.
事发十五分钟内
A cleaning crew sterilized the site
清洁人员对现场进行了消毒
within 15 minutes of the incident.
目前没有目击者
No witnesses have come forward.
如果有 我们会处理
And if they do, we'll deal with them.
就像你对托尼那样
The same way you dealt with Tony.
好了 动力
Come on, sport.
我不是一直都在照顾你吗
Haven't I always taken care of you?
欢迎 下一位
Welcome. Next.
抱歉 伙计
Oh. Sorry, mate.
看吧
Here you go.
枪不错 欢迎
Nice piece. Welcome.
下一个
Next.
过来
Come through.
我告诉你们
And I'll tell you something,
如果达科塔州的鲍勃·辛格当选总统
if "Dakota" Bob Singer gets elected president,
你就得向左翼社会主义者问好了
well, you say hello to left-wing socialism.
因为我现在就告诉你们
'Cause I'll tell you this right now,
他将完全遵循乔治·索罗斯的全球主义
he is gonna follow the George Soros globalist playbook to a T.
第一步 压迫公民 没收他们的枪支
Step one, oppress the citizens and confiscate their firearms.
第二步
Step two,
让所谓的新闻媒体大肆报道
have it all gleefully reported by the so-called news media.
- 假新闻 - 第三步
- Fake news! - And step three,
在全国的每一个教室里
in every classroom around the country,
他们会教你的孩子憎恨美国
they're gonna teach your kids to hate America,
憎恨宪法和第二修正案
the Constitution and the Second Amendment.
庆幸吧 沉默的大多数
Good for us, the silent majority,
和沃特步枪协会
and the Vought Rifle Association,
让我来告诉你们
let me tell you something,
我们全副武装 准备反击
we are armed and we're ready to fight back.
谢谢光临 女士们 先生们
Thank you for coming, ladies and gentlemen.
不要忘记 门口的空心弹 买二送一
Don't forget, two-for-one on hollow-points on the way out.
优惠码是"火药"
Use the promo code "Gunpowder".
上帝保佑你们
God bless y'all.
打扰了 火药先生 我是你的头号粉丝
Excuse me, Mr. Powder. I'm your number one fan.
你推销过的每把枪我都买了
I've bought all your rifles. Every one of them.
那把沃特VR-15
That Vought VR-15. Ooh.
真是一把好枪
That is a hell of a gun.
扳机尤其平滑
Smooth trigger pull.
平滑
Smooth.
我想和你握手 但...
I'd shake your hand, but, uh, well, you know.
我很感激
Well, I appreciate that.
你在复仇小队时 我就关注你了
Yeah, I followed you since your Payback days.
我是说 才十四岁
I mean, 14 years old,
你就被选为士兵男孩的副手
picked to be Soldier Boy's sidekick.
他是个伟大的人
He was a great man.
很高兴认识你 伙计
Well, it's nice meeting you, buddy.
你一定很开心吧
You must've been chuffed, eh?
帮助他完成任务
Helping him on his missions,
让他看你上厕所
letting him watch you on the bog,
把他的手指插进屁股
stick his finger up your bum a bit,
给他吹箫
give him a sloppy little nosh.
都是年轻副手的日常 不是吗
All in a day's work for a young ward, isn't it?
这些鬼话我早就听腻了
Like I haven't heard that sidekick pedo shit a thousand times before.
不如你帮我个忙 伙计 赶紧滚蛋
Why don't you do me a big favor, buddy, and fuck off.
你说的对 我很抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
只是肮脏 没有根据的谣言
That's a filthy, unsubstantiated rumor.
废话
Goddamn right it is.
以后就不是了
Till now.
这是你向沃特公司提的投诉书
This is a complaint you filed to Vought,
求他们解散复仇小队
begging to be taken off Payback
你的原话是 "士兵男孩习惯性的虐待"
on account of, and I quote, "Soldier Boy's habitual abuse."
依沃特的一贯行径 他们把这事压了下去
Of course they buried it, Vought being the cunts they are.
你这是个伪造的
That right there is a fake.
- 当然是真的 -不好意思 你是谁
- Course it is. - I'm sorry, who are you?
我说了 我是你的铁粉
I told you. Biggest fan.
而且我想帮你
And I want to help you.
保密
Keep shtum.
如果你的铁粉们发现
Be a crying shame if your red-meat faithful out there
你曾被士兵男孩性侵 你会沦为笑柄的
found out you were Soldier Boy's underage nob-gobbler.
现在 我只想知道
Now, all I want to know
他到底是怎么死的 告诉我
is what happened to him, and you're gonna tell me.
你就不怕我开枪
Or maybe I put a bullet in your head.
你敢开枪
You do that,
一个小时内就会传遍全网
and it'll be all over the Interweb within an hour.
兄弟 我才不在乎呢
See, buddy, I don't give a shit.
因为那种事从未发生过
'Cause that never happened.
士兵男孩从未侵犯过我
Soldier Boy never touched me like that.
靠
Fuck.
天啊 别跳
Oh, my God! Don't jump!
嘿 切尔西
Hi, Chelsea.
今天是你的幸运日
It's your lucky day.
因为
Well, considering.
你是我在我生日这天救的人
You're-you're my annual birthday save.
- 不要再靠近 - 生命是珍贵的礼物
- Don't come any closer. - Life is a precious gift.
就这样舍弃简直是打上帝的脸
To throw yours away would be a real slap in the Lord's face,
你不这么认为吗
don't you think?
你不想永堕地狱 是不是
You don't want to go to hell for all eternity, do you?
我是犹太人 我
I'm Jewish. I...
好吧 算了
All right, well, regardless,
就离楼边远一点 好吗
just step back from the ledge, please?
好的 这就行了
Okay, that's good.
大胆拍近景
Just don't be afraid of the zoom.
你又不是罗杰·狄金斯
You're not Roger Deakins.
迈克 把机器架起来 他随时可能飞下来
Mike, frame up. He could be flying down any second.
好的 没问题
Yep. You got it.
我靠
Oh, fuck.
得了 你看 我在这
Come on, look. I'm here now.
如果你跳的话 我也会飞下来接住你
If you jump, I'm just gonna fly down and save you anyway.
都是徒劳 而且
It's all futile and...
风暴女自杀
她 她不会
Sh-She wouldn't...
今天是我的生日
It's my... It's my birthday.
她
She...
你可能不知道 因为你是犹太人
You probably don't know this because, you know, Jew,
耶稣不是在圣诞节出生
but Jesus wasn't born on the 25th of December.
这种说法来自于异教徒 你猜怎么着
That was piggybacked off a pagan festival, and guess what.
今天也不是我的生日
Today is not my birthday, either.
不是
Nope.
不知道是哪一天 但他妈肯定不是今天
Don't know when it is, but sure as hell ain't today.
这只是市场部帮我选的
This was just chosen for me by a marketing department.
我根本没有生日
I mean, I can't even have a birthday at all.
我不是生出来的
I wasn't born.
是从他妈的试管里搞出来的
I was just poured out of a fucking test tube.
纯洁之胎
Immaculate conception.
我很清楚他的感受
I know exactly how he must have felt.
耶稣
Jesus.
你付出又付出
You give and you give...
付出了他妈一生
You give your whole fucking life,
然后呢
and what happens?
人们会毁掉你
People just tear you down.
人们为什么要摧毁他们的神
Why do people destroy their gods?
这公平吗 你得救了
H-How is it fair that you get saved,
另一个漂亮的 完美的神却死了
while a beautiful, perfect god gets killed?
你知道吗 切尔西
You know what, Chelsea?
我觉得你应该跳
I think you should jump.
我不想跳了
I-I don't think I want to.
你不想了
You don't want to?
为什么你不坚持一下自己的想法呢 切尔西
Why don't you show a little follow-through, Chelsea?
- 跳 - 拜托 我只想下来
- Jump. - Please, I... I just want to get down.
我不是在建议
I'm not suggesting anymore.
跳
Jump.
拜托 别
No. No, please.
上帝啊 上帝啊
Oh, God, oh, God.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
没有上帝
No God.
天上唯有我一人
The only man in the sky is me.
风暴女怎么会咬舌自尽呢
How the fuck did she bite off her own tongue?
像《百万美元宝贝》那样自尽了
Stormfront Million Dollar Babied herself.
- 太可怕了 - 那么
- That's horrible. - Oh, so...
老爸 有烟味
Daddy? It smells smoky.
没事 宝贝 交给我
It's okay, baby, I got it.
该死的
Fucking piece of shit.
别他妈响了
Shut the fuck up!
对不起
I'm sorry.
宝贝 对不起
Baby, I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 休伊 - 你好
- Hughie. - Hi.
- 嘿 你去哪了 - 呃
- Hey, where you been? - Uh...
就是
You know, just, um,
- 在家办公 - 天啊 你的手
- working from home. - Oh, my God, your hand.
嗯 不 没什么
Yeah. Yeah, no, that's... It's nothing.
- 我没事 - 所以 纳蒂亚是谁
- I'm fine. - So, who's Nadia?
纳蒂亚
Nadia?
斯科蒂说昨天有人来找纳蒂亚
Yeah, Scotty said some guy came in yesterday, asking for Nadia.
哦哦哦 不 是有一个人
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, no, there was, there was a guy,
他看着你的照片
um, and he... he was looking at your picture,
说你的名字是纳蒂亚 说他认识你
he said your name was Nadia, said he knew you...
很久很久以前就认识
from, like, way back when.
你不打算告诉我吗
You weren't gonna tell me?
是啊 我感觉可能
Uh, no, I mean, it was just some guy
这人忘吃药了
off his meds, seemed like, yeah.
对不起 你没来上班 还有你的手
I'm sorry, I-I mean, you're missing work, your hand.
- 发生了很多事吧 - 嗯
- Lot going on. - Hmm.
有什么我应该知道的吗
Is there something I should know?
他跟我在一起来着 很抱歉
He was with me. I'm sorry for stealing him
我借用了他一会儿
away from you, but...
我们有些事要讨论
we had some things that we needed to discuss.
事实上 动静闹的挺大
Very loudly, actually.
我们在潘娜拉大吵大闹一架
We made quite the scene at Panera.
没人认出我真是个奇迹
- Oh. - I mean, it's a miracle nobody recognized me.
对不起  我只是想保留一点
Yeah, sorry, I was, I was trying to preserve just a tiny,
自尊心 但是却吵了一架
little shred of my dignity, but, uh, we had a fight.
我们最后闹得不欢而散
We didn't leave things in the greatest place,
- 所以我想着过来 - 看看我吗
- so I thought I would come by and... - Check up on me?
- 人家担心你嘛 - 好吧 你知道
- Well, I was worried about you. - Yeah, well, you know I can
有些事情我可以自己处理 对吗
handle some things by myself, right?
我只是想帮忙
Okay, I'm just trying to help.
我并不总是需要你的帮助
I don't always need your help.
你不用一直把我当成孩子
I mean, you don't have to treat me like I'm a kid.
我还一直以为
Here I was thinking that I was
- 我把你当男朋友 - 你
- treating you like my boyfriend. - Well, you...
这跟我无关
You know, this is actually none of my business,
所以我先走了
so I'm just, I'm gonna go.
祝你们好运
Good-good luck with all of that.
- 还有休伊 - 是的
- Oh, and Hughie? - Yeah.
给她点空间
Cut her some slack.
你无需害怕一个强大的女人
You shouldn't be afraid of a powerful woman.
我的天
Oh my God.
谢谢你救了我 顺便说一声
Uh, thanks for the save, by the way.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
我来这干什么
What am I doing here?
阿莱克斯说你看起来很奇怪
Well, uh, Alex said that you were acting weird,
我每隔五分钟就给你打一个电话
and I've been calling you literally every five minutes.
- 所以 - 是的
- So... - Right.
靠 抱歉 在红河时我把手机关了
Shit. Sorry, I left my phone off at Red River.
我以为我们要一起解决此事
I thought we were gonna handle that together.
我知道
I know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 你的手在流血 - 我知道
- And you're bleeding. - I know,
因为我打不开罐头
because I can't open a fucking jar,
- 因为我什么事都做不好 - 休伊
- because I can't do anything fucking right. - Hughie.
怎么了
What's going on?
维琪是我朋友
Vicky was my friend.
我认识她女儿
I know her daughter.
她在办公室给我办过生日惊喜
She-she-she surprised me in the office on my birthday.
我们以前在办公室里一起打闹
We used to roll through that office
就像"触不可及"里那样
like we were the fucking Untouchables.
我以为事情终于按我的计划发展了
I thought things were finally, finally going my way.
天啊 我真是个天大的笑话
God, what a goddam joke I am.
嘿 不是这样的 休伊
Hey, that's not true, Hughie.
我可能还签署了一份领养文件
I may have signed us up to adopt a child.
嘿 看那里
Hey, look at that.
- 给你 - 七人队高塔
- There you go. - Seven Tower.
- 太棒了 - 再见 老爸
- Amazing. - Bye, Dad.
我爱你 宝贝
I love you, baby.
- 我也爱你 - 嗯
- I love you, too. - Mm.
好了
All right.
莫妮克在吗
Is Monique here?
莫妮克 马文来了
Uh, Monique, Marvin's here.
你想留下来一起看祖国人的生日特别节目吗
Hey, you gonna stay for Homelander's birthday special?
我烤了些香肠
I got some brats on the grill.
这次算了吧 谢谢
Think I'll pass, but thanks.
莫妮克 你知道我一直在努力
You know I've been trying, Monique.
努力离这些事情远远的
Been trying to stay away from all of it.
那些超人类
The Supes.
布彻
Butcher.
为了珍妮
For Janine.
- 也为了你 - 我知道
- And for you. - I know.
但是
But this...
士兵男孩的线索出现了
this Soldier Boy thing came up,
你知道我有心里阴影 我
and you know the baggage there, I...
我还想增加药量 就为了...
I tried upping my meds, just...
你又有那些可怕的想法了
You're having bad thoughts again.
还有痉挛和强迫意识
And the tics and the compulsions.
莫妮克 我在珍妮面前失去理智
Monique, I lost my shit in front of Janine.
就好像 士兵男孩就像是...
It's like, Soldier Boy, he's like this...
我头里的钢片 尤其是在他...
this steel sliver inside of my brain, after he...
我不知道该怎么办好
I don't know what to do.
你该回去找布彻
You need to go back to Butcher.
应该去
That's what.
我只是希望你能做回你自己
I never wanted to try to turn you into something you're not.
我讨厌你压抑自己
I-I hate that you're making yourself sick over it.
我可能不能再陪着你了 马文
Maybe I can't be with you anymore, Marvin,
真的很抱歉
and I am so sorry for that.
你还是要去做你该做的事
But you should go do what you have to do.
面对惨淡 坚持到底
Face this shit down.
千万别告诉珍妮
Please don't tell Janine about this.
什么都别说 还有我爸的事 都瞒着
About any of it. My pops, none of it.
我不想让她牵扯进来
I just want to leave her out of it.
珍妮会一直待在这里等你
Janine will be right here, waiting.
注意安全... 就算为了她
Just... stay safe for her.
风暴女说得对
Stormfront was right!
风暴女说得对 风暴女说得对
Stormfront was right! Stormfront was right!
今天 风暴女的追随者们在波特兰游行
The Stormchasers marched in Portland today,
数百人集结悼念风暴女
悼念逝去的英雄风暴女...
- mourning their fallen idol Stormfront... -
...人群之间突发暴力冲突...
...when violence broke out between...
宝贝 看
Mon coeur. Look.
看看这个
Look at this.
运行中的过山车
这是昆斯伯里的六旗游乐场 明天就去
Six Flags in Queensbury. We go tomorrow,
坐坐过山车 还有愤怒的恶魔
we ride the Greezed Lightnin' and, uh, Steamin' Demon
坐个够 最好把吃下肚的都吐出来
until we vomit the doughnut hamburgers, huh?
这和坐不坐过山车没关系
It was never about the roller coaster.
我明白
I know.
健二和我没有童年
Kenji and I didn't have a childhood.
我却对那个小姑娘和她哥哥
I just did the same thing to that little girl
- 做了同样的事 - 小姑娘
- and her brother. - Little girl.
- 不对... - 他们还能再保持童心吗
- No... - How can they ever be children again?
宝贝 别这么说
Mon coeur, no.
那不是你的错
That wasn't your fault.
我再也不是喜欢过山车的普通女孩了
I'll never be a normal girl who likes roller coasters.
我已经支离破碎 再回不到从前
I'm broken and can never be fixed.
都怪这剂毒药 深入我骨髓的诅咒
Because of this poison, this curse in my veins.
哥们儿 有点晚了 不好意思
Hi, buddy. I'm sorry I'm running late.
我还以为我能有空理个发
I thought I'd have time to sneak in a haircut.
实际上每次都比我预期的时间长
It always takes longer than I think it will.
储藏柜里有夹心饼干
There's some Double Stufs in the pantry,
但只能吃两块
but only two, mister.
超过两块 我肯定能发现
More than two, and I will know.
行吧 我得挂了
Okay. I'm hanging up now.
我就是想和你说 我爱你 咱们很快就能见面
Just wanted to tell you that I love you and I'll see you soon.
我爱你 咱们就快见面了
So, I love you, and I'll see you soon.
布彻
Butcher?
还好吗 兄弟
You all right, mate?
弗兰基和我说了绯红伯爵夫人的事
Frenchie told me about Crimson Countess.
到底什么情况
What the hell happened?
当时我们在追查线索 不过...
We was chasing down something, but...
我会收手的
I-I'm gonna knock it on the head.
那天 你说得对
Y-You was right the other day.
一切正常
Things are good.
瑞恩也没问题
Ryan's good.
我一开始就不该多管闲事
I should leave it well enough alone,
否则不会把一切都搞砸
before I go and fuck it all up.
还在吗
You there?
纽曼是超人类
Neuman's a Supe.
她是爆头者
She's the head popper.
- 什么 - 没错
- Yeah, what? - Yeah,
她相当于是斯坦·埃德加的女儿
she's pretty much Stan Edgar's daughter, too.
我去年一年都白费了
Past year of my life has been a waste.
我以为能公正地斗一斗沃特 其实做不到
I thought we could fight Vought the right way, but we can't.
都被他们算计了
It's all rigged.
如果要把他们搞垮
If we're gonna take them down,
必须不惜代价
we have to do whatever it takes.
用你的方式干
We have to do it your way.
布彻 听见我的话吗
Butcher, you there?
你他妈闹呢
You got to be fucking kidding me.
从我车上滚下来
Get your ass off of my car.
你为什么护着士兵男孩
Why you protecting Soldier Boy?
如果他真搞过我 我肯定把他剁碎了喂狗
If he'd have slipped me a length, I wouldn't hesitate.
绝不犹豫
I'd throw him to the fucking dogs.
就这
Oh, shit.
好了 别打了
Okay, okay.
求你
Please.
士兵男孩以前对我有点狠 知道吗
Soldier Boy used to slap me around a little bit, all right?
就是捉弄要入伙的人 玩得太过了 明白吗
It was just hazing that went too far, all right?
- 就这些 - 他到底发生了什么
- That's it. - What fucking happened to him?
出事的时候他没死 知道吧
He didn't die in an accident, all right?
核泄漏那整件事也是胡扯
The whole nuclear meltdown thing, it was just bullshit.
这个我他妈知道 他怎么死的
I fucking know that. What killed him?
不知道
I don't know.
我真不知道 他妈什么都不知道
I-I don't know! I don't fucking know!
明白吗 我们那会在尼加拉瓜
All right? We were in Nicaragua,
八四年 但我没看到
in fucking '84, but I didn't see it happen.
- 你一定看到了点什么 - 什么都没看见
- Well, you must have seen something. - I didn't see shit.
日 我当时就是个小屁孩
Fuck, I was just a kid.
你找别人问问 问中情局
Ask the others. Ask the fucking CIA.
- 中情局 - 是啊
- CIA? - Yeah.
我们当时给中情局做事
Yeah. We were working with the CIA.
谁负责
Who was the case officer?
格蕾丝
Grace.
格蕾丝 格蕾丝·马洛里
Grace... Grace Mallory.
明白吗 日
All right? Fuck.
听我说 等等
Look, please.
求你听我说...
Please, look...
我知道的都说了
Look, I told you everything I know.
行吗 求你了 别...
All right? Please, just-just...
我知道你都招了
I know you did.
但这改变不了你的所作所为
But it don't change what you are.
- 他这是穿了身什么玩意 - 太好了
- What the fuck is he wearing? - Yeah!
他这穿的是他妈什么玩意
What the fuck is he wearing?
太好了 来自超音速的献声
Yeah, all right. Let's hear it for Supersonic, everybody.
把服装部的人都他妈找来
Get me fucking wardrobe.
谁他妈负责服装的 我弄死他们
Get me fucking wardrobe so I can fucking choke them out!
现在我要为大家介绍我们的副队长
All right, so now, I would like to bring out our cocaptains.
掌声有请星光
So let's give it up for Starlight
以及今晚的风云人物 祖国人
and the man of the hour himself, Homelander!
- 生日快乐 祖国人 - 谢谢
- Happy birthday, Homelander. - Hey, thank you.
肥猪 我都看见你的米其林腰了 真恶心
- Yeah. - I can see your girdle, you disgusting fat fuck.
赶紧滚下台
Get off the fucking stage.
今晚和大家汇聚一堂 深感荣幸
Wow, I'm so honored to be with you guys tonight
谨以此为我的挚友和导师祖国人喝彩
to celebrate my dear friend and mentor Homelander.
我不仅要祝你生日快乐
I'm here to do more than wish you a happy birthday, though.
还要惊喜地宣布
I'm thrilled to be announcing
一项我无比珍视的项目
a project that is near and dear to my heart.
星光之家 一个非盈利基金项目
The Starlight House is a nonprofit foundation
专门襄助无家可归的人和高危青年
dedicated to helping homeless and at-risk youth.
祖国人 你的纳粹死了
Hey, Homelander! Your Nazi died!
他刚说他的纳粹死了吗
Did he just say his Nazi died?
跟我走
Let's go.
祖国人他...
Homelander...
他只是普通人
He's just, he's a human.
就像在座的各位一样
He's just like the rest of us.
人非圣贤 孰能无过
And we all make mistakes, right?
但我们都应该有重新来过的机会
But we all deserve second chances.
本着这一精神 祖国人同意
In that spirit, Homelander has agreed
捐出一千万...
to donate $10 million...
- 支持星光之家 - 不
- to the Starlight House, which is, I mean... - No.
- 鼓掌 掌声在哪里 - 不
- Give... Come on. Give it up. - No.
- 为他鼓掌 - 不 不是的
- Give it up for this guy. - No. No.
不
No.
星光刚刚撒谎了 没错 撒谎了
Starlight lied to you just now. She did.
我不会犯错
I don't make mistakes.
我跟"在座的各位"不一样
I'm not "Just like the rest of you."
我更强大 更聪明
I'm stronger. I'm smarter.
我更出色 更出色
I'm better. I am better.
我才不是什么爱哭鼻子的软蛋
I'm not some weak-kneed fucking crybaby
满世界没完没了地道歉
that goes around fucking apologizing all the time.
你们为什么非要让我装成这样
And why the fuck would you want me to be?
快进广告 罗杰 快他妈进广告
Go to fucking commercial, Roger. Go to fucking commercial.
你敢切走直播 罗杰
Don't you dare stop rolling, Roger!
我这辈子总有人想控制我
All my life, people have tried to control me.
整整一辈子
My whole life.
各种有钱有势有权的人
Rich people, powerful people
不让我说话 抹杀我的存在
have tried to muzzle me, cancel me,
让我显得无能 毕恭毕敬 拿我当个木偶
keep me impotent and obedient, like I'm a fucking puppet.
结果呢 做到了
You know what? It worked.
因为我允许这套机制有效
Because I allowed it to work.
说实话 如果他们能控制我
And guess what. If they can control me,
就一定可以控制你们
then you can bet your ass they can control you.
他们已经这么做了 只是你们不知道
They already do. You just don't realize it.
我受够了
I'm done.
我对道歉这套烦透了
I am done apologizing.
我受够了因为我有实力而饱受戕害的日子
I am done being persecuted for my strength.
你们这些人真该感谢上帝
You people should be thanking Christ
我之所以成为今天的我 就因为你们需要我
that I am who and what I am, because you need me.
你们需要我拯救你们
You need me to save you.
真话
You do.
也只有我有可能拯救你们
I am the only one who possibly can.
你们不是什么真英雄
You're not the real heroes.
我才是真正的英雄
I'm the real hero.
唯一的英雄
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现